So in my younger protest days, when people would see somebody who seemed like they were
basically just a plant to like start stuff, an agitator, they would point them out, you
know, similar to like when there are some hoes in this house, if you see them point
them out, if you see them point them out, please do that here on this app when you see
bots and the way you can recognize bots is literally they have a rhetoric that they will
just continue to repeat. And if they're black, I call them blots. So right now, the repetitive
rhetoric is why aren't you protesting Trump? And she's a private citizen. Any account that
you see saying that just respond bot, save yourself the energy, save yourself the energy. And I
see this all the time because on this internet, the bots, they have a flow. Like a few weeks
ago, the bot theme was telling me that I look old. So all of a sudden, I just started getting
all these comments all the time saying that I look old. So don't waste your energy. If
you see them point them out, if you see them point them out. Because let me just tell you
something. I don't know if you saw this, but they're gonna be busy pointing us out. So you
better start practicing.